WILLIAM KRASNOV

WWW.GITHUB.COM/WILLKOMAN

(267) 227-8466

WILLKOMAN@GMAIL.COM

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am a technologically skilled and outgoing hard worker with expertise with computers and am known to have great communication skills, whether it be with my fellow co-workers or clients. I always strive to optimize and streamline whatever I can to ensure a quick and simple experience for both the workers and the customers.

I've been known in my past positions for my charismatic nature and my willingness to perform exemplary work with minimal maintenance. I'm also extremely willing and enthusiastic to learn new skills and technologies I'm not currently familiar with, and have a very open mind.

SKILLS

- Computer Programming
- General Expertise w/ Computers
- Data Structures and Automation
- Office Expertise
- Data Analysis
- Statistical Knowledge

- Eloquent Communication Ability
- Excellent problem-solving and logical abilities
- Conflict Resolution

PROGRAMMING EXPERIENCE

- C# (5 years)
- Java (4 years)
- Unity Game Development (4 years)
- HTML5/CSS (2 years)
- JS (2 years)
- Swift/XCode (1 year)
- Python (1 Year)
- SQL (1 Year)
- Google Cloud Solutions (1 Year)
- React (6 months)

WORK HISTORY

JUNE 2019-2022

Junior Technical Support / Software Engineer Intern | SmartAdvocate | Port Washington, NY

- Served as a primary contact and assistant to clients and their technical issues with SmartAdvocate's software.
- Utilized SQL Server Management Studio to build queries to better improve client quality of life
- Developed minor subsystems to help streamline and improve the quality of SmartAdvocate

JUNE 2018-AUGUST 2018

File Clerk | Parker Waichman LLP | Port Washington, NY

- Implemented improvements to file systems and procedures.
- Located missing file materials.
- Tracked incoming and outgoing files and materials.
- Oversaw inventory and office supply purchases.
- Indexed, cataloged and stored physical records.
- Examined, categorized and sorted incoming documents.
- Maintained physical and computer-based filing systems.

June 2017-September 2017

Legal Assistant | Parker Waichman LLP | Port Washington, NY

- Contacted clients to schedule appointments and discuss the progress of cases.
- Worked as a team with attorneys, administrative assistants and fellow legal assistants.
- Developed software to better streamline the productivity of the legal team.

EDUCATION

2018

High School Diploma:

Sachem High School East, Farmingville, NY 3.4 GPA 2018-2020

Associate in Science:

Suffolk County Community College, Selden, NY 3.5 GPA 2020-2023

Computer Science B.S.:

SUNY Old Westbury, Old Westbury, NY